Angel Uray

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

aeucampos@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn | Angelist | Medium

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer with proven experience building deadline-driven projects while working remotely and asynchronously with worldwide teams, mastering my knowledge by mentoring junior development students on their journey simultaneously. Proficient in multiple languages, frameworks, and technologies, ability to quickly and efficiently scale my skills, even in fast-paced environments.

SKILLS

Front-End: JavaScript, React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3

Back-End: Ruby, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL

Tools & Methods: Git, GitHub, Render, Netlify, Mobile/Responsive Development, TDD, BDD, RSpec, Jest,

Chrome Dev Tools, React Dev Tools, Redux Dev Tools, Webpack, UML.

Professional: Remote Pair-Programming, Teamwork, SCRUM, Time-management, Self-taught.

EXPERIENCE

HIGHLIGHTED PERSONAL PROJECTS

Remote May 2022 – Present

Full Stack Web Development Student & Mentor

Proficiency in Full-Stack development subjects, including Algorithms, DS, Git, and Rails, while building multiple Full-Stack projects both independently and through pair programming with international teams.

Movies Webpage – Designed and developed a JavaScript-based Movies platform that allows users to search for any movie by retrieving real data from an API, as well as making comments, giving likes and dislikes, or getting current ratings, film dates, genre, and general descriptions about them.

Built with: CSS3, JavaScript, Webpack, Jest, and APIs.

CoinForU — Designed and Developed a React and Redux-based SPA, which allows users to check a list of cryptocurrencies and metrics by retrieving real data of any of them from the CoinGeckco API

Built with: CSS3, React.js, Redux.js, Jest, and APIs.

Space Traveler's Hub — Designed and Developed a SPA, that provides commercial and scientific space travel services, allowing users to book rockets and join selected space missions using real-life data from the SpaceX API.

Built with: CSS3, JavaScript, React, Redux, Jest, and APIs.

MICROVERSE
Mentor (Volunteer)

Remote July 2022 – Present

- Mentoring junior web developers, and providing technical support through code reviews.
- Suggest improvements to code organization and thus overall quality and performance.
- Provide tips and advice on how to maintain motivation and productivity under tight deadlines.

EDUCATION

MICROVERSE

May 2022 - Present

Remote Full Stack Web Development Program, Full Time

- Spent 1300+ hours mastering algorithms, data structures, and full-stack development while simultaneously developing projects with Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, React, and Redux.
- Developed skills in remote pair-programming using GitHub, industry-standard git-flow, and daily standups to communicate and collaborate with international remote developers.

SIMON RODRIGUEZ UNIVERSITY

Bachelor in Management mention in marketing (Incomplete)

July 2018 - January 2020